revenuewall.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy | RevenueWall

### Introduction

Opinion Capital, Inc. ("Company," "we," "our," or "us"), owns and operates the Websites www.opinioncapital.com, www.revenuewall.com, www.yoursurveysrouter.com, www.speakuprouter.com, www.cintsurveyrouter.com, www.revenuehut.com (the "Sites"). We know that your privacy is important to you.

Through the Site, we operate Opinion Capital ("Opinion Capital") through which we provide surveys that can be taken at the Site or via electronic notification methods such as, but not limited to, e-mail. We provide statistical sample to organizations that conduct research primarily for marketing or for social science purposes. We're committed to helping you understand how we manage and protect the information we collect. We take privacy seriously, and have taken many steps to help safeguard the information we collect from you.

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is provided to inform you of our policies and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and how that information is used. By using or accessing the Site and participating in Opinion Capital, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy and agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or participate in Opinion Capital.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you may contact the Opinion Capital Privacy Office at privacy@opinioncapital.com. If you have any Customer Service issues, please contact Customer Service here.

Our privacy policy will tell you about  

  * Opt-In to Opinion Capital
  * The Information We Collect and Use
  * Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * Communications from the Site
  * Rights Pertaining to Personal Information
  * Security and Information Protection
  * Privacy Policy for Children
  * Changes to this Policy
  * Contacting Us

Thank you for using Opinion Capital.

### Opt-In to Live Sample

Members may sign up for Opinion Capital by completing the "double opt-in" process at our Site(s) or through one of our many partners' Websites. During the double opt-in process, members are sent a confirmation e-mail following an initial request to subscribe at one of our Site(s) or one of our partners' Websites, and all members must affirmatively click an additional link in that confirmation e-mail - confirming their opt-in preference.

### The Information We Collect and Use

By information, we mean information about you collected through Opinion Capital and our Site, including "personally identifiable information" such as your name, e-mail address, residential or work address, certain demographic information, as well as information regarding your hobbies, interests and product ownership and other information you provide to us by registering for Opinion Capital, participating in our surveys or services, or making requests for information about our services. Registration for Opinion Capital is not required to view non-member areas of the Site. If you elect to register for Opinion Capital, we ask you for information that enables us to provide Opinion Capital. You will be registering with Opinion Capital on the form provided and such registration may require you to provide contact information such as your e-mail address, your name, and your residential or work address and certain demographic information. In addition, from time to time, we receive e-mail addresses from one of our partners, who may ask us to contact you to offer you a survey.

We may collect other "non-personally identifiable information" such as your user name and password (your "Login"), IP address, and your Website browsing patterns (discussed in further detail below). We use such non-personally identifiable information to serve you better and send you surveys that are most relevant to your interests. We and/or our data partners, where you have given such data partners your consent, may also seek other personally and non-personally identifiable information from you or where such information is otherwise publicly available.

From time to time we may use third-party providers to validate the accuracy of personal information you provide, so that we may offer a better statistical sample to our clients. We may use third parties to provide us with data they have collected about you, and append this data to your demographic profile. In such cases only a minimum amount of information is transferred to these third parties so as to enable them to perform specific functions on our behalf.

Additionally, in certain circumstances, we offer individuals the ability to participate in our client's surveys outside of Opinion Capital. If you are asked to participate in such a survey, we will request limited non-personally identifiable information about you. In some cases, after completion of the initial survey, we may request personally identifiable information about you in order to provide rewards, to offer you the opportunity to join Opinion Capital, or to participate in further surveys.

You may be referred to Opinion Capital or our surveys by one of our third-party business partners. In the event that we ask such partner to contact you with additional survey opportunities, we may share certain basic personal information that we understand such partner already maintains (such as your e-mail address and gender) as well as certain basic information regarding your Opinion Capital activity (such as the last time you completed a survey).

Any information provided to us will be retained and used solely for the purposes of fulfilling your requests, responding to your questions, offering you opportunities to participate in surveys, performing and carrying out the terms of Opinion Capital (including fulfilling any rewards), or communicating with you as a member of Opinion Capital.

We support the rights of our members by limiting the use of their information for legitimate market research purposes and we make every effort to conform to the efforts of the following organizations created to uphold ethical survey research

  * Marketing Research Association (MRA)
  * Council of American Survey Research Organizations (CASRO)
  * Advertising Research Foundation (ARF)

Opinion Capital, Inc. complies with the Canadian Privacy Act as set forth by the Department of Justice Canada regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Canadian residents. To learn more about the Canadian Privacy Act, and to view our certification page, please visit http://laws-lois.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/P-21/.

In compliance with the Canadian Privacy Act, Opinion Capital, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Canadian citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Opinion Capital, Inc. at:

  * Opinion Capital
  * Attn: Legal - Privacy Department
  * 1988 rue de la Plantation
  * Saint-Lazare, Quebec, Canada, J7T 3B4

### Member Profile

To further improve the quality, targeting and relevance of our surveys, you may be asked to provide certain demographic data (like your age, gender, postal code, income) and profile data (like occupation, shopping habits and other areas of interest) as certain surveys may be directed to those participants who meet a particular profile. You will be asked to answer certain questions on forms and pages hosted by us. The information we collect will be used to determine whether you are eligible to participate in the survey and will also be maintained by us to enable us to provide you with more relevant surveys in the future.

### Opt Out

Members can unsubscribe from Opinion Capital at any time, no questions asked. We know that just because you joined Opinion Capital a month ago doesn't mean that you necessarily want to stay on it forever. Every survey invitation we send is coded with a special footer that allows you to remove your name from Opinion Capital and services automatically by clicking a link provided in the message. In addition, you can discontinue your Opinion Capital membership by visiting <https://www.opinioncapital.com/unsubscribe> and following any instructions. Upon unsubscribing from Opinion Capital, we will deactivate your membership account and you will not receive any further survey invitations; although you may continue to receive some previously prepared survey invitations for a few days following the termination of your membership. We will retain your personal information for an indefinite period of time; however, we will continue to protect such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you would like your personal information deleted from our Site, please contact Customer Service at mailto:customerservice@OpinionCapital.com. We will respond to your request within 30 days. Please note we will not be able to delete data that has been archived, but we can delete current live information in our database.

### Aggregate Information

From time to time, we may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site and the Service, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they "click" on. We collect this information from you by "passive" means through the use of technologies such as "cookies" and IP addresses, which are discussed in greater detail below. We may also group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Site and Opinion Capital to our existing or potential business partners or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you, other list members or any other visitors to the Site.

### Data Sharing

Opinion Capital Inc. may share your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number (" **UID** "), postal code, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a " **Third Party MR Company** " and collectively the " **Third Party MR Companies** ") for the following purposes:

  * 1\. Identifying client survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the Third Party MR Companies; and
  * 2\. Disclosing such data elements to clients of the Third Party MR Companies for audience measurement services; 
  * 3\. Appending such data elements to completed client surveys and delivering the appended survey data to clients of the Third Party MR Company(ies) for analytical or research purposes.

If you are eligible for a client survey opportunity offered through a Third Party MR Company, the Third Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the client survey through the RevenueWall system. We will not share your name, email address, or phone number with the Third Party MR Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with a Third Party MR Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence, including, without limitation, in the United States, and by agreeing to this privacy policy you are agreeing to the processing and exportation of your personal information as set forth in this Section. If you have any questions about this data sharing please contact **support@revenuewall.com** or you can opt-out by clicking **Unsubscribe**. If you opt-out, it is the responsibility of us to inform the Third Party MR Companies. Please note that Opinion Capital Inc. is solely liable and responsible for managing all opt-out requests. Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the Third Party MR Companies.

### IP Addresses

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to third parties and to track the use of the Site. When visitors request pages from the Site or click on a link in a mailing sent through Opinion Capital our servers log the visitors' IP addresses. We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor or member when it will enhance the user’s experience or if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Site's policies or to protect the Company, the Site, the Site's visitors, Opinion Capital, our Internet Service Provider partners, the members or others.

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a Website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for a number of purposes.

**On Our Sites:** Most commonly, we use cookies to make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're using our Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard -you'll find them at most Websites. We use cookies on the Site to verify a member's login status. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Information such as the total number of visitors to the Site and pages viewed is most easily tracked with cookies. We may use the information from cookies to make improvements and updates to the Site and to tailor our services to our visitors', members' and survey participants' needs.

**For Banner Ads:** When you visit one of our Sites or take one of our surveys, without registering for Opinion Capital, we may place cookies on your computer that alerts Internet advertising networks that you have visited one of our Sites or surveys. These cookies, which do not track any personally identifiable information, allows us to ask Internet advertising networks to serve you advertisements with respect to survey opportunities, Opinion Capital and our Sites.

**For Brand Awareness Studies:** We may place cookies from a third-party technology provider on your computer that signals when you visit a Website that utilizes a supported Internet advertising network. We provide only limited non-personally identifiable information to the third-party technology provider, including certain demographic information and a coded user identification number. The signal emitted from the cookie includes solely the coded user identification number and the specific advertisement(s) that you may have viewed. Certain of our clients may ask us to send you survey opportunities to determine the effectiveness of their Internet advertising based on the signals sent by the cookie about the advertising you may have viewed. You may choose to opt-out of receiving these brand awareness cookies at any time by clicking on the following link: http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/6462?v=1&nt=0&nw=true. In the event you opt-out of receiving these cookies, we will no longer place brand awareness cookies on your system. As a registered member of Opinion Capital, we will save this opt-out preference to your profile.

By your use of the Site and Opinion Capital, you authorize cookies to be put in place and their use by us and our clients and business partners consistent with the disclosures above. The cookies will expire after one year.

You also always have the option of disabling the installation of new cookies and deleting existing cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent and to accept/reject such cookie(s) individually. However, please be aware that some features of the Site will not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies.

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons / Web Bugs)

Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly in HTML files and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

We may use clear gifs in our HTML-based e-mails to let us know which e-mails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications. We may also use them to confirm payment to our third-party partners. If you no longer wish to receive our communications sent by e-mail, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Except for the situations listed here in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties.

### Agents and Third-Party Service Providers and Partners

We may provide your personally identifiable information to a client or partner for limited market research related uses including, without limitation, modeling, validation, fraud detection and/or prevention, data append, database segmentation, and reward, incentive, or sweepstakes redemption, fulfillment, and/or entry in connection with your participation in or completion of any survey. In such instances, they are not permitted to retain or use your information for any other purpose.

### Digital Fingerprinting

We may use digital fingerprinting technologies to assign a unique identifier or "Machine-ID" to a user's computer to identify and track the computer. Opinion Capital works principally with a third-party provider to deploy this technology (the "Technology") and does not use it to collect personally identifiable information, or track the online activities, of the user of a computer; and will not disrupt or interfere with the use or control of a computer or alter, modify or change the settings or functionality of a computer. We use the unique identifier to assist our clients in ensuring the integrity of survey results. The third-party provider analyzes publicly available information and data obtained from the computer's Web browser and from other publicly available data points, including without limitation the technical settings of the computer, the characteristics of the computer, and the computer's IP Address, to create a unique identifier assigned to the computer. The unique identifier is an alpha-numeric ID. After creating the unique identifier, we do not retain the information analyzed by the Technology to create the unique identifier. Additionally, to assist our clients in protecting and ensuring the integrity of survey results, we (a) may link or associate your unique identifier to you and any of your personally identifiable information; (b) may share your unique identifier with our clients and with other sample or panel providers; and (c) may receive or obtain a unique identifier linked to you from a third party, including without limitation a sample or panel provider or a client of Opinion Capital. Any unique identifier(s) received or obtained by Opinion Capital and linked to a specific individual will be protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Change of Control / Asset Transfer

As the Company develops, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell all or parts of our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that the assets of the Company in whole or in parts are acquired by a third-party, customer information, including any visitor information collected through the Site or Opinion Capital, would be one of the transferred assets. In the event of a corporate change in control or sale of all or parts of our business assets our users will be notified and given the opportunity to opt-out of any such transfer of their personally identifiable information to the new corporate entity or asset purchaser.

### Legal and Site Compliance

The Company reserves the right to disclose member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the Company's rights or property, other visitors, list members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. The Company also reserves the right to disclose visitors or list member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. We may also use personally identifiable information to monitor compliance with the Sites' Terms and Conditions.

### Communications From the Site

### Survey Electronic Notification

We will send you targeted and relevant surveys by electronic notification (such as, but not limited to, e-mail, SMS, social media, smartphones) as is necessary to fulfill Opinion Capital to you.

### Service Notification

We will send you service-related announcements, which are not promotional in nature, on occasions when it is necessary to do so. For example, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send you electronic notification.

### Customer Service

Based upon the information you provide us, we will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, to fulfill incentive requests, and to manage your account. We may communicate with you by electronic communication or telephone.

### Rights Pertaining to Personal Information

We regularly send electronic notifications to the members of Opinion Capital. If you do not wish to receive them, you may opt-out and/or deactivate your account by following the instructions included in each communication.

### Security and Information Protection

The security of your information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it; however, no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Firewalls

Protecting the security of your personal information is very important to us. When we store information that you have provided to us when registering for Opinion Capital, that information is protected by security measures that include "firewalls" (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps keep unauthorized visitors from accessing information within our computer network), "intrusion detection systems" (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps detect any unauthorized visitors) and other tools such as data encryption and physical security, where appropriate. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data repository can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while the Company strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.

### Links to other sites

Please be aware that when you are on the Site, or when you receive an e-mail message from us through Opinion Capital, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There may be links to other sites from the Site' pages or from the e-mail message we send to you that take you outside our Site. These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there. Note that when you link to a third party site from the Site, you may see pre-populated data fields with your personal information; however, that information is not available to the third party unless you take certain actions on the third party's site, such as submitting a form.

### Single Sign-On

We use single sign-on service(s) that allow you to sign into Opinion Capital using your third-party social networking login credentials such as your Facebook or Twitter accounts. These services allow you to link your existing social network profile to your Opinion Capital account. Once linked, you will be able to post content on the third-party site from Opinion Capital and interact with your friends. If you choose to use such a sign-on service, Opinion Capital may also access certain profile information from your third-party social network profile such as friends, profile picture, etc.

### Privacy Policy for Children

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 on the Site or through the Service without permission from a parent or legal guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any information to us. If we become aware that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 without the permission of a parent or legal guardian, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

### Changes to this Policy

The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a notice on the homepage of the Site for a reasonable period of time after such changes are made, that this Privacy Policy has been updated, and by changing the "Effective" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes.

### Contacting Us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, please send them to the Opinion Capital Privacy office at privacy@OpinionCapital.com, or contact:

  * Opinion Capital
  * Attn: Legal - Privacy Department
  * 1988 rue de la Plantation
  * Saint-Lazare, Quebec, Canada, J7T 3B4
